chicksonright.com 2018-12-31

# Legal - Chicks On The Right

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which COTR, LLC (dba Chicks on the Right) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the chicksontheright.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by COTR, LLC (dba Chicks on the Right).

Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

Web browser cookies

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

If you would like to “opt out” of interest-based advertising delivered by advertisers on web pages using cookies, you may “opt out” by following the instructions available at [Network Advertising Initiative](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/).

Our Site uses third parties, including Facebook, who may use cookies, web beacons, and other storage technologies to collect or receive information from your websites and elsewhere on the internet and use that information to provide measurement services and target ads. You may opt-out of the collection and use of information for ad targeting. You may exercise your choice to opt-out by using the following links to [About Ad Choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices) and [Your Ad Choices](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/).

How we use collected information

COTR, LLC (dba Chicks on the Right) may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

To improve customer service  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.  
To personalize user experience  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.  
To improve our Site  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.  
To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature  
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.  
To send periodic emails  
We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.  
How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Google Analytics

This site participates in Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting which enables the site to collect data about traffic via Google advertising cookies and anonymous identifiers, in addition to data collected through a standard Google Analytics implementation. Both this site and third-party vendors may use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) or other first-party identifiers, and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together.

Visitors may opt-out of the Google Analytics Advertising Features through Ads Settings, Ad Settings for mobile apps, or via Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on.

Changes to this privacy policy

COTR, LLC (dba Chicks on the Right) has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

Contacting us

Any unsolicited emails sent to the owners of COTR have the potential to be published and credited with or without name/contact information.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
COTR, LLC (dba Chicks on the Right)  
chicksontheright.com  
mockarena@chicksontheright.com
